威尔: 你知道吗？ 是结对编程的时候了,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: You know what?
It is pair programming, it's time,
我们的节奏很好很好,
we're taking this very nicely paced,
it's wonderful,
我们要做一些结对编程，伙计们。
we're gonna do some pair programming,
folks.
我觉得现在回到原来的舞伴身边,
I think at this point,
get back back with your same partners,
去 csbin.io/closures 你会看到我们在这里做了什么
go to csbin.io/closures and
you're gonna see what we did here, and
你会看到一大堆关闭的挑战。
you're gonna start to see a whole
bunch of closure challenges.
在20分钟的结对编程会议之后,
Right after a 20 minute
pair programming session,
我们会一起回来，看看结局如何
we're gonna come back together and
we're gonna see how closure works
我们说的是词汇范围。
under the hood and
we're talking lexical scoping.
我要告诉你们一个五个字母的单词，而不是一个五个字母的单词，单词短语
I'm going to tell you the one five letter
word, not a word five, word phrase that
威尔，我不会再开这个玩笑了，因为显然有人对此很不高兴
will, I'm not to make this joke anymore
because somebody apparently was upset that
他们知道这个词，肯定不会得到高级开发人员的职位。
it definitely did not get them a senior
developer job for knowing this phrase.
说话人2: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 那么，如果你知道
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So but if you know
这句话，你会得到这样的高级开发工作，我想保证
this phrase, you will get a senior
developer job like that, I want to promise
你现在只要说出这五个字，你就会在另一个国家看到。
you right now you say those five words,
you're gonna see it in another country.
好了，回到结对编程。
All right, back to pair programming.